

DANG THI HOAI

SEO CONTENT WRITER INTERSHIP

PROFILE INFO

I am a senior student of the Faculty of Foreign Languages, majoring in Business Language.

Currently, I want to take an internship at the company to apply the knowledge I have learned at university to reality. That is how I can gain experience from the seniors in the company, accumulate and improve myself every day.

CONTACTS



02/03/2002





0386568572



hoaidt0203@gmail.com



Tran Khat Tran St, Thanh Nhan,

Hai Ba Trung, Hanoi

ACADEMY BACKGROUND

NATIONAL ECONOMICS UNIVERSITY

- Major: Business English
- GPA: 3.5/4.0
- 2020-2024

WORK EXPERIENCE

SALE ASSISTANT QCS Auto (Mar 2021-Oct 2021)

- · Copywriting, product promotion on the company's Facebook page
- · Product consulting to customers
- Track input and output products
- Meet monthly KPI
- · Complete weekly reports for managers

PART-TIME ENGLISH TEACHER HOCMAI education Inc. (Sep 2022-Now)

- Teaching English to primary, secondary and high school students
- Compiling learning materials
- parents' complaints, Handle provide appropriate solutions and alternatives

WORK SKILLS

- Language: English IELTS 7.0, Chinese
- Office computer skills: Word, Canva, Powerpoint, etc.
- Familiar with smart digital devices
- Teamwork skills: able to work individually and in groups
- Flexible, adaptable to new changes
- Self-study skills



ĐẶNG THỊ HOÀI

THỰC TẬP SINH SEO CONTENT WRITER

THÔNG TIN CÁ NHÂN

Em là sinh viên năm cuối khoa Ngoại ngữ kinh tế, chuyên ngành Tiếng Anh thương mại.

Hiện tại em muốn đi thực tập tại công ty để áp dụng những kiến thức đã học ở trường đại học vào thực tế. Đó là cách em có thể học hỏi kinh nghiệm từ các anh chị trong công ty, tích lũy và hoàn thiện bản thân mỗi ngày.

LIÊN HÊ



02/03/2002





0386568572



hoaidt0203@gmail.com



Trần Khát Chân, phường Thanh

Nhàn, Hai Bà Trưng, Hà Nôi

HOC VẤN

TRƯỜNG ĐẠI HỌC KINH TẾ QUỐC DÂN

- · Chuyên ngành: Tiếng Anh thương mại
- GPA: 3.5/4.0
- 2020-2024

KINH NGHIỆM LÀM VIỆC

TRƠ LÝ BÁN HÀNG QCS Auto (T3/2021-T8/2021)

- · Viết quảng cáo, quảng bá sản phẩm trên trang Facebook của công ty
- Tư vấn sản phẩm cho khách hàng
- Theo dõi sản phẩm đầu vào và đầu ra
- Đáp ứng KPI hàng tháng
- · Hoàn thành báo cáo hàng tuần

GIÁO VIÊN PART-TIME **HOCMAI** education Inc. (T9/2022-Nay)

- · Dạy tiếng Anh cho học sinh tiểu học, THCS, THPT
- Biên soạn tài liệu học tập
- Xử lý khiếu nại của phụ huynh, đưa ra các giải pháp và giải pháp thay thế phù hợp

KỸ NĂNG LÀM VIỆC

- Ngoại ngữ: Tiếng Anh IELTS 7.0, Tiếng Trung
- Kỹ năng vi tính văn phòng: Word, Canva, Powerpoint, v.v.
- Kỹ năng làm việc nhóm: có khả năng làm việc cá nhân và theo nhóm
- Khả năng tự học